A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 1953-2004
Library of Virginia
- II. Commissioner's Correspondence and Subject Files, 1995-2003., Extent: 37 cubic feet (37 boxes). (Box 61-97)
  - 2001
    - National Tobacco Grower Settlement Trust (Box 90)
    - Memorandum of Understanding between VDACS and the Tobacco Commission (Box 90)
    - Minutes - Tobacco Idemn. and Com. Revit. Commission (Box 90)
    - Tobacco Idemn. and Com. Revit. Commission (Box 90)
    - Tobacco Warehouses (Box 90)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (Box 90)
    - Travel, Blanket (Box 90)
    - Travel Process Review Team (Box 90)
    - USDA (2) (Box 90)
    - USDA (1) (Box 90)
    - VP1 and SU (Box 90)
    - Animal Industry Services (Box 91)
    - Butts, Donald W. (Box 91)
    - Consumer Protection (Box 91)
    - Consumer Affairs Annual Report (Box 91)
    - Alvarez, Andy - Consumer Affairs (Box 91)
    - Office of Dairy and Foods (Box 91)
    - Consumer Affairs Report on Activities, 2000 (Box 91)
    - Endangered Species (Box 91)
    - Feasibility Study, Piedmont-Roanoke Regional Shipping Market for Fruit (Box 91)
    - Pesticides (3) (Box 91)
    - Pesticides (2) (Box 91)
    - Pesticides (1) (Box 91)
    - Lawson, Marvin - Office of Pesticide Services (Box 91)
    - Pesticide Fees - Refund (Box 91)
    - Rogers, Alan - Office of Product and Industry Standards (Box 91)
    - Fulgham, Frank - Office of Plant and Pesticide Services (Box 91)
    - Sleight, Thomas (Box 91)
    - Division of Marketing (Box 91)
    - Brussels Office (Box 91)
    - Commodity Services (Box 91)
    - Grain Grading (Box 91)
    - Office of International Marketing (Box 91)
    - Fruit and Vegetable Fees (Box 91)
    - Peanut Inspection Fee Schedule (Box 91)
    - Accomplishments - Governor (Box 91)
    - Accomplishments - VDACS (Box 91)
    - Accounts, Dept. of (Box 91)
    - Agreement (Facilities) between Virginia Public Building Authority and Commonwealth of Virginia (Box 91)
    - Agreement Between Agriculture Marketing Services, USDA and VDACS (Box 91)
    - Agreement Between Dept. of Army and Commonwealth of Virginia Regarding Aquatic Plants (Box 91)
    - Agreement between VDACS and Virginia Boll Weevil Eradication Foundation, Inc. (Box 91)
    - Agreement - CCC, VDACS and USDA, Emergency Food Assistance Program (Box 91)
    - Agreement - Grant, Virginia State Dairymen's Association and VDACS (Box 91)
    - Memorandum of Agreement - VDACS and DCR, Natural Heritage Endangered Species (Box 92)
    - Agreement - VDACS and City of Chesapeake, Plastic Pesticide Container Recycling Plan (Box 92)
    - Agreement of Understanding - VDACS and Prince George County, Plastic Pesticide Container Recycling Program (Box 92)
    - Agreement Between VDACS and Dept. of Game and Inland Fisheries (Box 92)
    - Agreement Between VDACS and General Services, Space (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Understanding Between VDACS and USDA (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Agreement Between VDACS and USDA, Burley Tobacco (Box 92)
    - Agreement Between VDACS and Virginia Dept. of Health Professions and Funeral Directors (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Understanding Between VPI and SU and VDACS (Box 92)
    - Agreement Between VDACS and Virginia Tech Dept. of Agriculture and Applied Economics (Box 92)
    - Agreement - Donna Whitmarsh and VDACS (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Agreement Between VDACS and Dept. of Conservation and Recreation (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Agreement Between VDACS and Carroll County (Box 92)
    - Agreement Between VDACS and Dept. of General Services (Division of Consolidated Labs) (Box 92)
    - Agreement Between Virginia Bright-Flue Cured Tobacco and Tobacco Association (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Understanding Between VDACS and DGS (Division of Engineering and Buildings) (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Agreement Between VDACS and the Library of Virginia (Box 92)
    - Agreement Between VDACS and Dept. of Minority Business Enterprise (Box 92)
    - Agreement Between VDACS and Dept. of Social Services, Community Work Experience (Box 92)
    - Agreement Between VDACS and VDOT (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Agreement Between VDACS and City of Suffolk (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Understanding Between VDACS and Dept. of Environmental Quality (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Agreement Between VDACS and VSU (Box 92)
    - Agreement - VDACS and Federal Crop Insurance Corporation (Box 92)
    - Agreement Between VDACS and Virginia Tech re: Food and Fiber Industry (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Agreement Between VDACS and Isle of Wight County (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Understanding Between VDACS and Virginia (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Understanding Between VDACS and USDA, Packers and Stockyards Program (Box 92)
    - Memorandum of Understanding Regarding Bovine Embryos from the US to Indonesia (Box 92)
    - Agenda - SMT (Box 92)
    - Agriculture Economic Assistance Act (Box 92)
    - Virginia Agriculture Vitality Program (Box 92)
    - Virginia Apple Board (Box 92)
    - MOU - Virginia Apple Board (Box 92)
    - Apple Feasibility Study (Box 92)
    - Aquaculture (Box 92)
    - Aquaculture Bill (Box 92)
    - Atlantic Rural Expo (Box 92)
    - Attorney General's Office (Box 92)
    - Domestic Preparedness Work Plan (Box 92)
    - YMCA (Box 92)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council (Box 92)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 92)
    - Virginia Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services (Box 92)
    - Virginia Farmers Market Board (Box 92)
    - Virginia Pest Control Board (Box 92)
    - Virginia Marine Products Board (Box 92)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation (Box 92)
    - Virginia Turkey Committee Board (Box 92)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board (Box 92)
    - NASDA (Box 92)
    - SASDA (Box 92)
    - SUSTA (Box 92)
    - Suggested Response (1) (Box 93)
    - Suggested Response (2) (Box 93)
    - Suggested Response (3) (Box 93)
    - Suggested Response (4) (Box 93)
    - Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services Meetings (Box 93)
    - J. Carlton Courter, III (2) (Box 93)
    - J. Carlton Courter, III (1) (Box 93)
    - J. Carlton Courter, III (3) (Box 93)
  - 2002
    - Delmarva Conservation Corridor (Box 94)
    - Disasters (3) (Box 94)
    - Disasters (2) (Box 94)
    - Disasters (1) (Box 94)
    - Decision Brief, Chronic Wasting Disease of Elk and Deer (Box 94)
    - Education, Dept. of (Box 94)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of (Box 94)
    - VDACS Emergency Response Manual (Box 94)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 94)
    - Environmental Quality, US Dept. of (Box 94)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of (Box 94)
    - Food and Drug Administration (Box 94)
    - EEO Committee (Box 94)
    - Farm Bureau Federation of Virginia (Box 94)
    - Nicole Casal - FOIA (Box 94)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 94)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of (Box 94)
    - General Services, Dept. of (Box 94)
    - Governor's Office (Box 94)
  - 2003
    - Accounts, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - Academic Excellence Final Report (Virginia Tech College of Agriculture and Life Sciences) (Box 95)
    - Agenda - SMT (Box 95)
    - Agriculture Net Receipts Presentation (Box 95)
    - Agreement - Information Network Services and VDACS (Box 95)
    - Agreement - USDA Agriculture Marketing Services and VDACS (Box 95)
    - Apple Board, Virginia (Box 95)
    - Annual Report - Performance Management Advisory Committee (Box 95)
    - Attorney General's Office (Box 95)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts (Box 95)
    - Awards Committee - VDACS (Box 95)
    - Biosecurity (Box 95)
    - BSE (Box 95)
    - Capital Outlay Projects, 2004-06 (Box 95)
    - USDA Catfish Feed Assistance Program (Box 95)
    - Eastern Shore Marketing and Inspection Office, Capital Outlay 2004-06 Biennium (Box 95)
    - Education, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - Emergency Services, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - VDACS Emergency Response Manual (Box 95)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - Environmental Quality, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - eVA Project (Box 95)
    - Farmers Market System Report 2002 (Box 95)
    - Farm Bureau Federation, Virginia (Box 95)
    - Farmers Market System, Virginia (Box 95)
    - Food and Drug Administration (1) (Box 95)
    - Food and Drug Administration (2) (Box 95)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) (Box 95)
    - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - General Services, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - Governor's Office (Box 95)
    - Health, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - Homeland Security (Box 95)
    - Homeland Security (Box 95)
    - Homeland Security Grant (Box 95)
    - Virginia Horse Center (Economic Impact) (Box 95)
    - Horse Council, Virginia (Box 95)
    - HJR 159 (1) (Box 95)
    - HJR 159 (2) (Box 95)
    - House of Representatives (US Congress) (Box 95)
    - Human Resource Management, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - Information Technology Strategic Plan, VDACS 2002-2004 (Box 95)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - Interior, US Dept. of (Box 95)
    - Internal Auditor, Dept. of (Box 95)
    - Interstate Pest Control Compact, Annual Report (Box 95)
    - Interstate Pest Control Compact, 2003 Interim Financial Report (Box 95)
    - Virginia Invasive Species Workgroup (Box 95)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Committee (JLARC) (Box 95)
    - Virginia Winegrowers Advisory Board (Box 95)
    - Virginia Pesticide Control Board (Box 95)
    - Virginia Poultry Federation (Box 95)
    - NASDA (Box 95)
    - Capital Implementation Plan (Box 96)
    - Cattle Industry Board (Box 96)
    - Charity Food Advisory Board (Box 96)
    - Combined Virginia Campaign (CVC) (Box 96)
    - Commission on Local Government (Box 96)
    - Commonwealth Management Institute (Box 96)
    - Comptroller's Office (Box 96)
    - Conservation and Recreation, Dept. of (Box 96)
    - Consumer Affairs Advisory Committee (Box 96)
    - USDA Specialty Crop and Agriculture Promotion Grants (Box 96)
    - Coyote Damage Control Report (Box 96)
    - Dairy Compact (Box 96)
    - Dairymen's Association, Virginia (Box 96)
    - Delegates (Box 96)
    - Delmarva Conservation Corridor (Box 96)
    - Delmarva Poultry (Box 96)
    - [Disasters] (Box 96)
    - Disasters (Box 96)
    - Disaster Assistance to Virginia Farmers, Report, 11/03 (Box 96)
    - Virginia Drought Assessment and Response Plan (Box 96)
    - Hurricane Isabel (Box 96)
    - Drought Assessment and Monitoring Plan (Box 96)
    - Land Use (Box 97)
    - 2003 Legislative Guidelines (Box 97)
    - Legislative Services, Dept. of (Box 97)
    - Library of Virginia (Box 97)
    - Meat Inspection Budget Reduction (Box 97)
    - MOU - AI-Delmarva (Box 97)
    - MOU - Shore to Shore Program (Box 97)
    - Milk Commission (Box 97)
    - Natural Resources, Secretary of (Box 97)
    - Organic Certification (Box 97)
    - Parker, Brenda (Box 97)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of (Box 97)
    - Regulatory Review - Executive Order 25 (Box 97)
    - Risk Management Agency, USDA (Box 97)
    - Secretary of Administration (Box 97)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth (Box 97)
    - Secretary of Technology (Box 97)
    - Secretary of Technology, Surveys and Information (Box 97)
    - Secure Virginia Panel (Box 97)
    - Report to the Senate Finance Committee (Box 97)
    - Senators (Box 97)
    - Sole Source (Box 97)
    - Solem, Christine (Box 97)
    - Southern States (Box 97)
    - State Fair (Box 97)
    - Southeast Farmers Market (Box 97)
    - Southeastern Virginia Farmers Market Coop (Box 97)
    - Strategic Planning (Box 97)
    - Task Force - Food Safety (Box 97)
    - Tobacco (Box 97)
    - Tobacco Trust Certification Board (Box 97)
    - National Tobacco Grower Settlement Fund (Box 97)
    - MOU - VDACS and Tobacco Commission (Box 97)
    - Minutes - Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission (Box 97)
    - Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission (Box 97)
    - Transportation, Dept. of (Box 97)
    - Travel, Blanket (Box 97)
    - USDA (1) (Box 97)
    - USDA (2) (Box 97)
    - Virginia Cooperative Extension Emergency Response IT Network (Box 97)
    - Washington Building Space Utilization (Box 97)
    - VPI and SU (Box 97)
    - Water Plan (Box 97)
    - Virginia Agriculture Council (Box 97)
    - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 97)
    - Virginia Farmers Market Board (Box 97)
    - Virginia Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services (Box 97)
- III. Board Correspondence and Minutes, 1958-1998., Extent: 9 cubic feet (9 boxes). (Box 98-106)
  This series is arranged roughly chronologically and contains agendas, minutes and correspondence related to the Virginia State Board of Agriculture and Commerce and Virginia Board of Agriculture and Consumer Services. The series consists of agendas, correspondence, memorandum, meeting notes, notes, presentations, and reports.
  - Board Meeting, 16-17 April 1958, Roanoke (Box 98)
  - Lynchburg Board Meeting, 16 April 1958 (Box 98)
  - Roanoke Board Meeting, 17 April 1958 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 24 September 1958 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 6 February 1959 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 1 July 1959 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 21 August 1959 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 25 January 1960 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 13 December 1960 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 19 July 1960 (Box 98)
  - Hearings, Giant Foxtail, 18 January 1961 and 18 October 1961 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 21 August 1961 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 27 September 1961 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 23 January 1962 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 17 December 1962 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 30 October 1962 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 27 February 1963 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 9 August 1963 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 10 April 1964 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 18 December 1963 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 31 July 1964 (Box 98)
  - Board Actions, July 1964 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 3 December 1964 (Box 98)
  - Board Report, Regulatory Reform Information (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 12 March 1965 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 21 April 1966 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 28 March 1968 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 24 September 1968 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 7 November 1968 (Box 98)
  - Board Meeting, 24 July 1969 (Box 98)
  - Public Hearings, 26 September 1977 (Box 98)
  - VDAC Board Meeting, 22-23 September 1975 (Box 99)
  - Board Meeting, 26-27 February 1992 (Box 99)
  - Board Meeting, 26-27 September 1977 (Box 99)
  - Board Meeting, 15 October 1982 (Box 99)
  - Board Meeting, 11-12 December 1979 (Box 99)
  - Board Meeting, 27-28 September 1983 (Box 99)
  - Board Meeting (orientation), 23 July 1983 (Box 99)
  - Board Meeting, 21 April 1983 (Box 99)
  - Board Meeting, 15-16 December 1982 (Box 99)
  - Board Meeting, 25-26 September 1978 (Box 100)
  - Board Meeting, 19 September 1979 (Box 100)
  - Board Meeting, 16 December 1981 (Box 100)
  - Meeting, July 1981 (Box 100)
  - Patti Heffler, 1982 (Box 100)
  - Extension Service and Dean Nichols Meetings, 2-3 September 1981 (Box 100)
  - Board Meeting, 16-17 December 1980 (Box 100)
  - Board Meeting, 22-23 September 1980 (Box 100)
  - Board Meeting, 12 December 1978 (Box 100)
  - Board Meeting, 30 September 1992 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 9 July 1992 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 20 May 1992 (Box 101)
  - Board Information, General, 1990-1991 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 7-8 December 1989 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 6-7 December 1990 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 26 September 1990 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 22-24 July 1990 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 15-16 May 1990 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 21-22 February 1990 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 8-10 July 1992 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 20 May 1992 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 5-6 December 1991 (Box 101)
  - Board of Agriculture Meeting, 2 October 1991 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 21-23 July 1991 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 23 May 1991 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 20-21 February 1991 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 26-27 February 1992 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 8 December 1992 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 7 December 1993 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 29 September 1993 (Box 101)
  - Board Orientation, 3 September 1993 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 18-20 July 1993 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 30 June 1993 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 19-20 May 1993 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 17-18 February 1993 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 8 December 1992 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 30 September 1992 (Box 101)
  - Board Meeting, 27 September 1995 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 5-7 July 1995 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 28 April 1995 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 25-26 April 1995 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 11 January 1995 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 7 December 1994 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 28 September 1994 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 24-26 July 1994 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 18 May 1994 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 22-23 February 1994 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, February 1997 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 20 February 1997 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 11 December 1996 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 11 December 1996 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 2 October 1996 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 21-23 July 1996 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 16 May 1996 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 14 February 1996 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 15 May 1997 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 15 May 1997 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, July 1998 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 14 May 1998 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 10 July 1997 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 14 March 1984 (Box 102)
  - Board Meeting, 29-30 October 1981 (Box 103)
  - Public Hearing, 16 December 1980 (Box 103)
  - Board Meeting, 22-23 February 1983 (Box 103)
  - Board Meeting, 24-25 September 1984 (Box 103)
  - Board Meeting, 13-14 December 1983 (Box 103)
  - Board Meeting, 10 August 1983 (Box 104)
  - Public Hearing: Dog Pound Guidelines, 1982 (Box 104)
  - Board Meeting, 21 February 1979 (Box 104)
  - Board Meeting, 8 May 1979 (Box 104)
  - Dues and Subscriptions (Box 105)
  - Personnel, 1982 (Box 105)
  - 1982-1984 Budget, New Needs (Box 105)
  - Role Clarification Workshop, 7-9 October 1981 (Box 105)
  - A.D.P. (Box 105)
  - A.D.P. (Box 105)
  - [no label] (Box 105)
  - 1982-84 Budget Training Session, 7 October 1980 (Box 105)
  - 1978-80 Budget (Box 105)
  - 1980-82 Budget Material (Box 105)
  - Purchases, Inventory, et. al (Box 105)
  - 1982-84 Budget Information (Box 105)
  - [no label] (Box 105)
  - Miscellaneous loose papers (Box 105)
  - Board Meeting, 29 April 1980 (Box 106)
  - Board Meeting, 25 May 1983 (Box 106)
  - Board Meeting, 18-19 December 1984 (Box 106)
- IV. Commissioner's Speeches and Correspondence, 1968-1998., Extent: 3 cubic feet (3 boxes). (Box 107-109)
  This series contains speeches and related correspondence by the Agriculture Commissioner. The remarks are arranged roughly chronological.
  - ca. 1981 (Box 107)
  - ca. 1979-1980 (Box 107)
  - 1979 (Box 107)
  - ca. 1982 (Box 107)
  - 1983 (Box 107)
  - 1970-1974 (Box 107)
  - 1983 (Box 107)
  - ca. 1985-1987 (Box 107)
  - Nurseries, 1968 (Box 107)
  - 1976-1977 (Box 107)
  - 1975 (Box 107)
  - 1979 (Box 107)
  - 1978 (Box 107)
  - 1979 (Box 107)
  - 1976 (Box 107)
  - 1977 (Box 108)
  - 1973-1975 (Box 108)
  - 1993-1998 (Box 109)
- V. Special Interest Items, 1953-2001., Extent: 3 cubic feet (3 boxes). (Box 110-112)
  This series contains miscellanous subject files. Notable subjects include: information on droughts in Virginia from 1953 to 1993.
  - Organic,1996-2001 (Box 110)
  - Poultry, 1998-1999 (Box 110)
  - Family Food Dollar, 1971 (Box 111)
  - Farm Bill, 1992 (Box 111)
  - Farm Bureau Federation, 1973 (Box 111)
  - Farm Cooperatives, 1965-1968 (Box 111)
  - Farm Finance, 1972-1980 (Box 111)
  - Farmers Home Administration (Box 111)
  - EPA (Box 111)
  - Mike Espy, 1993 (Box 111)
  - Exports (Box 111)
  - Exotic New Castle Disease (Box 111)
  - Emergency Resource Management Plan (Box 111)
  - Endangered Species Act (Box 111)
  - Extension (Box 111)
  - Extension Services (Box 111)
  - Environmental Health (Box 111)
  - EIA Board Hearings, 1980 (Box 111)
  - Electricity (Box 111)
  - Electronic Marketing (Box 111)
  - Emergency Disease Era. (Box 111)
  - EBDC (Box 111)
  - EDB - Ethlyene Dibromide (Box 111)
  - Economic Poison and Ecology - Annual Reports (Box 111)
  - Economic Review (Box 111)
  - Egg Quality (Box 111)
  - 1988 Drought (Box 112)
  - 1989 Drought (Box 112)
  - 1991 Drought (Box 112)
  - 1993 Drought (Box 112)
  - Duck Virus Enteritis (Duck Plague), 1992 (Box 112)
  - Earthquake History, Virginia (Box 112)
  - 1966 Drought (Box 112)
  - Drought Situation, 1963-1964 (Box 112)
  - 1980 Drought (Box 112)
  - 1983 Drought (Box 112)
  - 1986 Drought (Box 112)
  - 1987 Drought (Box 112)
  - 1953-1954 Drought (Box 112)
  - Department History (Box 112)
  - Dog Pound Guidelines, 1980 (Box 112)
  - E.C. Downes (Box 112)
  - 1977 Drought (Box 112)